杰森:我只是说如果要加班两星期的话,
Jason: I'm just saying that I wouldn't be going in to work tomorrow if
明天我就不去工作了.
I were two weeks over due.
麦琪:因为你比我更适合当个好妈妈.
Maggie: Well that's because you are a better mother than I am.
迈克:嘿.
Mike: Heee.
本:迈克,记住,唱歌是为了孩子,答应我别瞎唱.
Ben: Mike. Singing is for kids. Besides you promised no singing. Remember.
迈克:嗨,谁在唱歌?我只不过在说嘿嘿嘿.
Mike: Hey, who's singing? All I said was Heeeee.
本:别和我吵,迈克.爸爸妈妈说了,今天是我的生日.
Ben: Quit it mike. Like mum and dad said. It's my day.
迈克:好,好.你的聚会,你的规则.嘿.
Mike: Alright, alright. It's your party, it's your rules. Heeeee.
本:迈克!
Ben: Mike!
杰森:宝贝,你讲起话来像个医生.
Jason: Honey speaking as a doctor...
麦琪:杰森,杰森,杰森,杰森.吃点心时保持安静.
Maggie: Jason, Jason, Jason, Jason. It's silent cake time.
杰森:我只是说你知道的和我一样多,
Jason: I'm just saying that you know as well as I do,
你不也总是说"就是这"嘛.
the big "this s it" moment could come at any time.
麦琪:那是.你又生过几个孩子?
Maggie: Really. And how many babies have you had?
杰森:我不想推它,这样做是愚蠢的……我不多说了.
Jason: I'm not going to push it. Going into work is stupid and ...enough said.
麦琪:杰森,这孩子还没出生.哦,我可怜的小南瓜.
Jason, the baby will not come... Oh I'm sorry pumpkin.
不说肚里的孩子了,我们说过,今天属于你.
No more talk about the new baby. Like we said, it's your day.
本:谢谢.
Ben: Thank you.
杰森:那就赶紧吧,许个愿.把蜡烛吹灭.
Jason: So come on. Make a wish. Blow out the candles.
本:我许好了.
Ben: I got it.
开萝尔:你们真的还没想好孩子的名字吗?
Carol: Have you guys really not decided on any names for the baby?
杰森:开萝尔.
Jason: Carol.
开萝尔:怎么了?我说什么了?
Carol: What? What did I say?
迈克:这比嘿嘿更糟糕.
Mike: It was a lot worse than Heeeee.
本:迈克!
Ben: Mike!
杰森:什么是嘿?
Jason: What is Heee?
迈克:那只是一个词,爸爸,很明显本会因此生气.
Mike: It's just a word dad, that apparently seems to be freaking Ben out. And you know what
你们知道最近对他说了哪些废话吗.
crap you guys have been with him lately.
杰森:等一下.
Jason: Now wait a minute...
开萝尔:迈克,你为什么总这样……?
Carol: Mike. Why do you always have...?
杰森:你们的妈妈要生孩子了,这是我们全家的一件大事.
Jason: Your mother's having a baby, it's a big strain on the whole family.
所有人:(同时谈论)
Everyone: (talking at the same time)
杰森:他要是生气,你们别责怪他.
Jason: You can't blame him for acting a little irrational.
本:男士们!我们需要一个新西维尔.
Ben: Man! Just what we need. A new Seaver.
麦琪:这儿坚持住.就在这.
Maggie: Hold on here. This is it.
杰森:这是什么?
Jason: This is what?
麦琪:杰森.
Maggie: Jason.
杰森:你确信?
Jason: Are you sure?
麦琪:我确信,杰森.
Maggie: I'm sure. Jason.
杰森:好的,车里有汽油.就是这,她说是这.
Jason: Yes, well there's gas in the car. This is it, she said this it.
麦琪:喔,另一边.
Maggie: Wow. Another one.
开萝尔:哦,我的上帝.
Carol: Oh my god. Sorry.
杰森:现在每六分钟子宫收缩一次,你还好吧?
Jason: Contractions are six minutes apart now. You're ok?
麦琪:嗯.
Maggie: Uh hu.
杰森:麦琪,我曾经告诉过你,
Jason: Maggie, did I ever tell you that back in medical school,
我上医学院时,想了很多关于妇产科的问题.
you know I thought an awful lot about oscentrics and gynecology.
麦琪:你是说过.
Maggie: I bet you did.
开萝尔:我真不明白你们两个怎么会如此冷静.我的意思说,
Carol: I still don't see how you two can be so calm.
妈妈,你快要生了.
I mean mum, you are about to give birth.
这可能是整个世界最痛苦,最重要的经历.
Perhaps the most painful, gross experience in the whole world.
麦琪:谢谢你,开萝尔.
Maggie: Thank you. Carol.
杰森:你们的妈妈和我之前已经有过好几次经验了,开萝尔.
Jason: Your mum and I have the advantage of having gone through this a few times before, Carol.
开萝尔:是的,但是你们那时候更年轻.
Carol: Yeah, but you were much much younger then. Sorry.
麦琪:开萝尔,这和年龄无关.
Maggie: Carol, age has nothing to do with it.
当你准备好时,你就可以从容面对.
When you are prepared for a situation you can take anything in your stride.
迈克:我很好,别担心我.说真的,
Mike: I'm ok. Don't worry about me. In fact, don't worry about anything.
什么都不用担心.妈妈,
Mum, I got your suitcase here, and doctor Goodners phone number.
我把你的箱子拿来了,还有医生的电话号码.已经万事俱备.
Everything's set.
开萝尔:连迈克都这么镇静.我想我是要病了.
Carol: Even Mike is calm. I think I'm going to be sick.
迈克:记住,你需要什么,我都在你身边.我不怕血,
Mike: And remember, if you need anything, I'm here.
内脏,脓,或者其他什么东西.
I'm not afraid of blood or guts or puss or anything.
麦琪:迈克,你知道你能做什么吗?你可以烧点热水.
Maggie: Mike, you know what you could do? You could heat me some water.
迈克:水.热水?你是说孩子马上就要出生了?好的,
Mike: Water. Hot water? You mean the babies coming right now?
爸爸,你是一位医生,你不能让它慢点吗?
Well, dad, you're a doctor. Can't you stop that thing?
麦琪:迈克,我只是想喝些茶.
Maggie: Mike, I just want some tea.
迈克:茶,哦.我可以做.茶,嘿,本.妈妈好像要在卧室里生孩子.这是一件大事情,我曾经考虑过生命这种礼物.
Mike: Tea. Oh. I can do that. Tea. Hey Ben. Mum is like ready to give birth in the living room. This is major stuff here. And to think, I used to think the gift of life was sea monkeys.
开萝尔:我终于明白了.我知道为什么妈妈和爸爸看起来这么冷静,
Carol: I finally figured it out. I did.
他们在演戏.
I know why mum and dad are acting like they're so calm. It's an act.
那是演戏,表面文章.
A cover.
迈克:你试试看.
Mike: Cover this.
开萝尔:哦,那是真的,迈克.装成一个无所谓的乡巴佬.
Carol: Oh, that's right Mike. Act like the insensitive lout that you are.
迈克:开萝尔,如果你声音再大点,只有狗才能听见你了.
Mike: Carol, if your voice gets any higher, only dogs will be able to hear you.
开萝尔:迈克尔?西维尔,我希望那是一个女孩,和我一模一样.
Carol: Michael Seaver. I hope it's a girl. With every ounce of my being.
迈克:我不能接受.
Mike: Well, I don't stand a chance.
麦琪:哦,杰森!现在还不行.
Maggie: Oh Jason! This can't be happening now.
杰森:为什么不?
Jason: Why not?
麦琪:我们还得挑出名字来.
Maggie: we still have to pick out names.
杰森:你应当早就考虑好.
Jason: Well you should have thought about that before you went into labor.
迈克:好了,古德讷医生等着我们呢.你知道她是女的吗?
Mike: Right, doctor Goodner knows we are on our way. Did you know she was a woman?
杰森:是的.赶紧,大家都过来,上我的车,来.
Jason: Yes. Hurry, come on everyone. In my car. Come on.
迈克:不,不.我们不进你的车.你的车在店里.
Mike: No, no. We can't go in your car. Your car's in the shop.
杰森:怎么回事?
Jason: What's it doing there?
迈克:你让我开过去的.
Mike: You told me to take it there.
杰森:哦,那是上星期,迈克.
Jason: Oh that was last week mike.
迈克:你还说我从来都不听话.
Mike: And you say I never listen.
杰森:好了,我们乘你妈妈的车.出发吧.
Jason: Alright, we'll take your mothers car. Let's go.
开萝尔:但是你讨厌开她的车.
Carol: But you hate driving her car.
杰森:不,我不讨厌.
Jason: No, I don't.
麦琪:是的,你讨厌.
Maggie: Yes, you do.
杰森:是的,我讨厌,但是这次是去医院.
Jason: Yes I do, but it's just to the hospital.
麦琪:我不想委屈你.
Maggie: I don't want to put you out.
迈克:听好了,我们可以坐我的车.怎么样?
Mike: Look, we can take my car. Alright?
杰森:好,好的.我们出发吧.
Jason: Yeah, alright. Let's go.
迈克:下不为例,如果我们因为超速而被拦下,最后我要声明,我从来没有
Mike: for once, if we are stopped for speeding, I can finally say...ah not that I ever get
因为超速被拦下.
stopped for speeding.
杰森:我来驾驶迈克的车.
Jason: I'll drive mikes car.
开萝尔:但是迈克的车我们不能全都坐下.
Carol: But we all won't fit in Mike's car.
麦琪:那么我也驾驶我的车.
Maggie: T hen I'll drive my car too.
杰森:太好了!
Jason: Great!
麦琪:很好.
Maggie: Great.
杰森:不!
Jason: No!
麦琪:不?
Maggie: No?
杰森:不,麦琪.
Jason: No Maggie.
麦琪:但是我必须去,我才是主角……哦!
Maggie: But I have to go. I'm the one that's...oh!
杰森:哦!
Jason: Oh!
麦琪:哦!
Maggie: Ohhhhh!
众人:哦!
Everyone: Oh!
迈克:好了,我们快成爸爸的精神病人了.好了,爸爸.你带妈妈坐我的车,我坐开萝尔的车.
Mike: Ok, we are starting to sound like a bunch of dads mental patients. Ok dad. You take mum in my car, and I'll take carol's car.
开萝尔:我没有车.
Carol: I don't have a car.
迈克:我是说我带你坐妈妈的车.
Mike: I meant id take you in mum's car.
杰森:本怎么办?
Jason: What about Ben?
迈克:本不会开车.
Mike: Ben can't drive.
开萝尔:我们差点忘了本.
Carol: No, we almost forgot Ben.
本:差点?
Ben: Almost?
杰森:你带他坐你的车,因为我来开你们妈妈的车,真的.
Jason: You take him in your car, because I'll be taking mums car, which is really...well is that your car...
麦琪:杰森!
Maggie: Jason!
众人:好吧.
Everyone: Ok.
开萝尔:来,本.我们永远等你.
Carol: Come on Ben. We can't wait forever.
本:我想呆在家里.今晚看电视.
Ben: I think I'll just stay. I was going to watch TV tonight anyway.
迈克:本,你得停止看电视,开始一种新的生活.
Mike: Ben, you got to stop watching TV and start living your life.
本:电视就是我的生活.
Ben: TV is my life.
杰森:对不起.我是杰森 西维尔,我的妻子约了古德讷医生,她快要生孩子了.
Jason: Excuse me. I'm Jason Seaver and my wife is a patient of doctor Goodners and she's going to have a baby.
护士:不!
Nurse: No!
麦琪:医生还没来?
Maggie: Is the doctor here yet.
护士:是的,她正在洗手.
Nurse: Yeah, she's scrubbing up.
你不是电视新闻的主持人麦琪 马隆吗?
Aren't you that Maggie Malone from the TV news?
麦琪:是的.
Maggie: Yes.
护士:我经常看你的节目.
Nurse: I see you all the time.
麦琪:谢谢.
Maggie: Thank you.
Nurse: I didn't say I 矢ike you. I said I see you.
护士:我可没说喜欢你,我只是看你.
杰森:好了,我们只是来看病,不相干的事情以后再聊.
Jason: Ok, can we just get on with the medical routine. We'll save the cystic enembral stuff for later.
护士:好.看吧,一个想对别人友好的人,遭受这样的回报.
Nurse: Fine. See a person tries to friendly to someone and you see what
现在,在我们给你做准备之前,马隆太太.
happens. Now, before we take you off for prepping, Mrs. Malone.
麦琪:西维尔太太.
Maggie: Mrs. Seaver.
护士:反正都是你.我们医院里,
Nurse: Oh, you are one of those.
有间育婴室.
Anyway, this hospital has what is called a birthing room.
杰森:好的,我和妻子已经告诉给孩子们了.
Jason: Yes. My wife and I have told the kids all about it.
护士:先生,我可以工作了吗?
Nurse: Sir. Can I please do my job?
现在,
Now, this birthing room allows the whole family to be a part of,
这育婴室允许全家人待在那,亲眼看到生育的过程.
and witness to, the beauty of birth.
开萝尔:喔!
Carol: Oooh!
护士:确实是这样.
Nurse: Exactly.
麦琪:哦.
Maggie: Oh!
杰森:孩子要生了.
Jason: Now this kid wants out.
护士:本尼,又有一个产妇,我们开始吧.
Nurse: Bernie, we got another customer. Let's roll.
开萝尔:好,好.
Carol: Alright, alright.
迈克:,好的,妈妈,你会平安的.
Mike: Ok mum, you'll be fine.
开萝尔:祝你好运.
Carol: Have fun.
麦琪:谢谢.
Maggie: Thanks.
开萝尔:别忘了箱子.
Carol: Don't forget the suitcase.
迈克:别担心,爸爸.我会和紧张的开萝尔待在这儿,爸爸,别忘了你的相机.
Mike: Don't worry dad. I'll stay here with nervous little Carol. Dad you forgot your camera.
画外音:约翰逊医生,叫你的经纪人.
Voice: Doctor Johnson, call your broker.
开萝尔:观看一个孩子出生真是太恐怖了.
Carol: Watching a birth would be so fleshy.
迈克:就像在3D中看外国人.
Mike: It's kind of like watching Alien in 3D.
开萝尔:我想你留在这,是因为必须有人待在这,照顾紧张的我.
Carol: I thought you were staying here cos, cos someone has to stay here with nervous little Carol.
迈克:如果这能使你更开心,开萝尔,那么我走.你可以和本待在这儿.
Mike: Well if it will make you happier Carol, then I'll leave. And you can stay here with little Ben.
画外音:泽格勒医生,请进来.
Voice: Doctor Zeigler, call admissions.
迈克:好了,开萝尔,你把本怎么了?
Mike: Alright carol, what did you do with Ben?
开萝尔:我?
Carol: Me?
迈克:你!开萝尔,
Mike: Me! Carol, this is no time to be thinking about yourself.
现在没时间考虑你自己.他刚才是和我们在电梯里吗?
Now, now was he in the elevator with us?
开萝尔:我,我,我不记得.
Carol: I, I, I don't remember.
迈克:你,你今天怎么了?
Mike: I I I, what is it with you today?
开萝尔:好,为什么本总是想逃跑呢?
Carol: Alright, now why would Ben pick now, of all times, to run off?
迈克:我不知道.
Mike: Well I don't know.
也许他很难过,他怕有了小宝宝以后,
Maybe he's upset because he thinks with the new baby;
我们不会有足够的时间陪他了.
he thinks maybe we don't have time for him.
开萝尔:真糊涂.有了小宝宝,
Carol: Well that's silly.
我们不会有时间忍受本的糊涂.
With the new baby, we don't have time for Ben's silliness.
迈克:开萝尔,如果你想成为孩子的成长顾问,可千万别.
Mike: Carol, if you ever think about becoming a child counselor, don't.
开萝尔:看你,你想待在这儿欺负我呢,
Carol: Look, do you want to stay here and insult me,
还是去找本?
or do you want to go look for Ben?
迈克:开萝尔,我做什么并不重要.
Mike: Carol, what I want does not matter here. Ok?
好吧,我来查这一层,你查其余八层.
Now I'll check this floor and you go check the other eight.
开萝尔:其余八层?
Carol: The other eight!
迈克:你去过哪儿了?
Mike: Where have you been?
开萝尔:我已经查完了八层.你做了什么?
Carol: I had eight floors to check. What have you been doing?
迈克:检查这一层的每一个角落,你无法相信我在小卖部看见了一位老太太在做什么.
Mike: Checking every nook and cranny on this floor. And you'll never believe what I saw this old lady doing in the supply room.
开萝尔:好了,本现在还在这家医院吗?
Carol: Alright, now bens got to be some place obvious.
迈克:不会,我已经检查过了.食堂这个小时不开放.
Mike: No, I already checked. The cafeteria's not open at this hour.
我想我们应该告诉爸爸妈妈你把他弄丢了.
Well I guess we're just going to have to tell mum and dad that you've
lost him.
开萝尔:我把他弄丢了!
Carol: I lost him!
迈克:很好,你承认了.
Mike: Good, you admit it.
开萝尔:我们还不能告诉他们.
Carol: We can't tell them anything now.
迈克:你傻了?他们的一个孩子丢了.
Mike: Are you out of your mind? One of their children is missing.
开萝尔:哦,来,迈克.你不觉得他们有些忙吗?
Carol: Oh come on Mike. Don't you think that they are a little busy?
迈克:忙什么?哦!
Mike: With what? Oh!
画外音:沃勒医生,请来报到.
Voice: Doctor Waller, report to OR.
本:你们都自以为是.
Ben: You guys think you are so cute.
医生:小家伙,小家伙,你不应该来这儿.
Doctor: Kid, kid. You don't belong here.
本:这是公事.
Ben: It's official.
麦琪:啊,闭嘴,杰森!
Maggie: Ah, shut up Jason!
杰森:谢谢你,医生.
Jason: Thank you doctor.
医生:别客气,医生.
Doctor: You are welcome doctor.
杰森:哦,加油,麦琪,你能行.
Jason: Oh! Come on Maggie, you can do it.
麦琪:你能行!这能让我感觉好一点吗?你以为自己是教练?
Maggie: You can do it! That's supposed to make me feel better? You call yourself a coach?
杰森:很好,麦琪,别想你的痛苦.
Jason: That's good Maggie. You take your mind off your pain.
麦琪:不想我的痛苦.
Maggie: Take my mind off my pain. Ok.
好,
Do you know how annoying it is to be married to someone with your toilet
你知道嫁给有你这样上厕所习惯的人有多苦恼.
habits?
杰森:不,什么?
Jason: No. What?
麦琪:你总是让卫生间里的马桶盖竖起来.你想过没有,我不喜欢坐在水里.
Maggie: You always leave the damn seat up in the damn bathroom. You'd think that after all this time, you'd get it through your thick scull that I don't enjoy sitting down in water.
麦琪和杰森:(发出噪音)
Maggie and Jason: (making noises)
医生:他让马桶盖竖起来.我的第一任丈夫也是如此,他卫生纸用完从来也不换一卷.
Doctor: He leaves the seat up. That's what did it in my first marriage. Does he leave half a sheet on the roll without replacing it?
麦琪:从不.
Maggie: Constantly.
医生:男人都是些孩子.
Doctor: Men can be such babies.
杰森:谈到孩子,我们还能对付这一个吗?谢谢.
Jason: Speaking of babies, can we just get on with this one? Thank you.
开萝尔:好了,迈克,我们到了.
Carol: It's ok Mike. We got the right room this time.
杰森:你们好,进来.本在哪儿?
Jason: Hi kids. Come on in. Where's Ben?
迈克:本,啊,我是说本.
Mike: Ben. Ah, I mean Ben.
开萝尔:我们来这儿,当然不是为了找他.
Carol: We're certainly not here looking for him.
杰森:他在哪儿?
Jason: Where is he?
迈克:食堂.
Carol: The waiting room.
开萝尔:等候室.
Mike: The cafeteria.
迈克:等候室.
Mike: The waiting room.
开萝尔:食堂.
Carol: The cafeteria.
迈克:他在食堂等候.
Mike: He's waiting in the cafeteria.
杰森:来这儿让他有一些恐惧.
Jason: A little squeamish about coming in hu?
迈克:好的,我们无论如何也要找到他.
Mike: Yeah. We got to tare this place apart until we find him.
开萝尔:我明白.
Carol: I know.
杰森:你们去告诉他,待在这并不可怕.
Jason: You just go tell him it's not so scary being in here.
迈克:我刚才一直都想告诉你,开萝尔.
Mike: I've being trying to tell you for the last hour Carol.
麦琪和杰森:(发出分娩的声音)
Maggie and Jason: (making birth noises)
画外音:苏利文医生,叫你的妻子.
Voice: Doctor Sullivan calls your wife.
病人:小家伙.你能把那个东西捡给我吗?我弯不了腰.
Patient: Damn. Yo pal. Can you fetch that for me? I don't bend over so good.
本:好的.
Ben: Uh yeah.
病人:谢谢你.
Patient: Thanks, I owe you.
本:你能在医院吸烟吗?
Ben: Can you smoke in a hospital?
病人:你是一位医生?
Patient: Are you a doctor?
本:不是.
Ben: No.
病人:护士?
Patient: A nurse?
本:不是.
Ben: No.
病人:公务员?
Patient: An orderly?
本:不是.
Ben: No.
病人:那我就可以在医院里抽烟,你叫什么来着?
Patient: I can smoke in a hospital. So who the hell are you?
本:本 西维尔.
Ben: Ben Seaver.
病人:本 西维尔!本 西维尔?
Patient: Ben Seaver! The Ben Seaver?
本:你听说过我?
Ben: You've heard of me?
病人:没有,本 西维尔,你在这做什么?
Patient: No. So Ben Seaver, what are you doing here?
本:不做什么.
Ben: Nothing.
病人:好,如果你进来,我们可以吹牛聊天.
Patient: Ah good. If you come in we can chew the fat.
本:吹牛!我减了10磅了.
Ben: Fat! I lost ten pounds.
病人:我是说谈话,聊天.近来,这里不错吧?顺便说一下,我叫克里斯 格尼,你可以叫我克里斯.
Patient: I mean talk, jaw, chat. Get down. Come in. Nice place hu? Oh, by the way, I'm Chris long shot Gaynee. You can call me Chris.
本:好的.
Ben: Ok.
病人:我来猜一下,你在医院里到处逛,是想找些吃的.
Patient: So, let me guess, you wander hospitals for a living?
本:不.
Ben: No.
病人:你不太爱说话,是吧?
Patient: You're not much of a conversationalist, are you?
你有一些事?
You got some problems?
本:我不知道.
Ben: I don't know.
病人:哦,
Patient: Oh come on.
来.你是我在这儿见到的手上不拿针的第一个人.
You're the first person I've seen around here without a needle in his hand.
也许我能帮你解决问题,
Maybe I can help you out with your problem. It would make me feel better.
这会让我感觉心情舒畅.我喜欢听别人谈心事,
You know I love to have guys tell me their problems.
我就靠这养活自己.
That's what I do for a living.
本:我爸爸和你一样.
Ben: My dad does the same thing.
病人:别开玩笑.他也是酒吧招待?
Patient: No kidding. He's a bar tender too?
迈克:这儿发生了什么?我肯定吸入了一些麻醉剂或者其他一些东西.
Mike: I don't know what that must have been. I must have inhaled some of the anesthesia or something.
杰森:是的.
Jason: Yeah.
开萝尔:可能是你的臭袜子.
Carol: Probably your socks.
杰森:你现在给我安静点,好吗?
Jason: Now I just want you to take it easy for a while. OK?
麦琪:对不起,杰森,这儿还有一位病人.
Maggie: Excuse me Jason, there is another patient here.
杰森:哦,好的,好的.你是我的特殊病人,我唯一的病人.
Jason: Oh yes, yes. This is my special patient. My one and only patient.
开萝尔:你们不像帮我找本吗?
Carol: You're not going to wimp out of helping me look for Ben, are you?
迈克:开萝尔,我和你一样焦急.
Mike: Carol, I am just as concerned as you are about the little pus bucket. Alright?
本:克里斯,我甚至没能打开我的礼物,他们甚至没唱歌给我听.
Ben: You know Chris, I didn't even get to open my presents. They didn't even sing to me.
病人:哦,本,本,本,别这样.
Patient: Oh, Bennie, Bennie, Bennie. Pull yourself together.
本:这让我很伤心.
Ben: Hit me again.
病人:你会开车吗?
Patient: You're not driving, are you?
本:啊?
Ben: Hu?
病人:酒吧招待的玩笑.
Patient: Bar tender joke.
本:我不懂,克里斯,
Ben: I don't get it Chris. I just don't get it.
我真得不懂.
I mean I figured it would be alright with this new kid coming,
我本来以为多了个小家伙是件好事,可是他已经顶替了我.
but he's crowding me already.
病人:他甚至还没生下来.
Patient: And he's not even born yet.
本:好的!我意思是我本来是西维尔家中最年轻的一个,
Ben: Right! I mean I've been the youngest Seaver my whole life.
在那之前,大家都宠着我,
Before that, I was nothing. Now with this new kid coming, what am I now...
现在来了个新人,我将什么也不是了.
nothing.
病人:没关系!来,
Patient: Nothing! Come on Bennie, you're getting carried away.
本,你想得太多了.别这样伤心.
That's not the milk talking is it?
本:我得面对,我被代替了.
Ben: I got to just face it. I'm being replaced.
你有饼干吗?
You wouldn't have any cookies to go with this would you?
病人:如果让他们看见,他们会让我吃泻药.
Patient: If they catch me with these, they are going to give me a physic.
本:什么是泻药?
Ben: What's a physic?
病人:你不用知道,吃饼干吧.听着,本,我们已经是朋友了,我告诉你一些事,我可不会告诉每个人.在我做酒吧招待的这些年里,我看到了很多,老的,小的,什么都有.我学到的最重要的一课就是,所有那些老话都是正确的,时间可以治愈所有的创伤,生活还得继续.12岁大的孩子不会听你.我知道今天是你的生日,我没有时间包装你的礼物.但是把它收下吧?这是一个老人的建议.我要告诉你,我什么都做过,酒吧招待,士兵,打过官司,坐过牢,我至今不知道是为什么.另外,我还是一位丈夫,父亲,儿子.但是你知道我最喜欢做什么吗?哥哥.
Patient: You don't want to know, eat the cookies. Now look, Bennie pal. Since you and me go back a long way, I'm going to tell you something I don't tell everybody. You know in all my years as a bar tender, I've seen a lot of things. Youth, age, birth, and everything else. And the biggest lesson I've learned is, well, all those old clichés are true. Time does heel all wounds. Life does go on. Twelve year olds do not listen to you. Now look, cos I didn't now it was your birthday, I didn't have time to wrap your present. But take it anyway hu? It's a little advice from an old man. You know, I'll tell you, I've been a lot of things; a bar tender, a veteran, a cowanian, or is it a Rotarian, I can never get that right. Also, I've, I've also been a husband, a father, a son. But you know the thing I enjoyed being best? A big brother.
本:哥哥.
Ben: Big brother.
病人:你有哥哥吗?你觉得他怎样?
Patient: You got a big brother? What do you think of him?
本:哦,他是最好的.
Ben: Oh he's the best.
虽然他把我当成笨蛋,但是我认识的最伟大的人.
He treats me like a doofus, but he's the greatest guy I know.
病人:现在想一下,有人也会这样看待你有多好,即使你把他当成傻瓜.
Patient: Now think about how nice it will be to have someone around who thinks that same way about you. I mean, even if you did treat him like a goofus.
本:是笨蛋.
Ben: Doofus.
病人:无论如何,本 西维尔,
Patient: Whatever. Ben Seaver, you are a lucky man.
你是一个幸运的人.你不会被取代,
You are not being replaced. You're being added on to.
而只会有人依赖于你.嘿,这不是你每个生日都能得到的礼物.
Hey pal, this is not a gift you are going to get every birthday.
从现在开始,去做一个本哥哥吧.
From now on, you are going to be Big Brother Ben.
本:本哥哥?
Ben: Big Brother Ben?
病人:在我当酒吧招待时我学到的另一样事情是,如果你不能解决别人的痛苦,
Patient: Another thing I've learned as a bartended is that if you can't
就试着帮助他忘掉.为了做到这点,
solve a guys problem, try and help him forget it.
我有一大堆的顶级笑话.保证会让你大笑不止.
So as a result of that I happen to have a top shelf of top shelf
你准备好了吗?什么东西四条腿,
jokes. Guaranteed to crack the sourest pus into hysterical laughter.
一条尾巴,和犬吠声.
You're ready? What's got four legs, a tail, and barks?
本:狗.
Ben: A dog.
病人:你听说过.
Patient: You heard it.
杰森:用力,麦琪,用力.
Jason: Push Maggie. Push.
医生:我能看见头了.
Doctor: I can see the head.
麦琪:哦,杰森,我再也不想这样了.
Maggie: Oh Jason, I'm never going through this again.
杰森:你生了迈克之后也这么说.用力,开萝尔,用力,还有本.
Jason: Oh that's what you said after Mike. Push. And Carol. Push. Oh and Ben.
医生:好了.
Doctor: Well done.
麦琪:杰森,这不是四十岁的女人该做的事了.
Maggie: Oh Jason, this is not something that a forty year old woman should do.
医生:你想要男孩,还是女孩?
Doctor: You want a boy, or you want a girl?
杰森:你有什么?
Jason: What have you got?
病人:好了,我认输.如果你知道大象和犀牛杂交后生什么的话?
Patient: Alright, I give up. What do you get if you cross an elephant with a rhino?
本:犀牛象.
Ben: An elephino.
病人:行了,行了.这里,
Patient: I got it, I got it. Here, shuffle these will you. Now listen.
你洗一下牌.听着,我大概不应当告诉你这个,
I probably shouldn't tell you this one, but,
但是,你曾见过得最漂亮的女孩步行进了酒吧,打扮得像条鱼.
the prettiest girl you ever saw walks into a bar dressed like a fish.
本:五元纸币,我想那是你的五元纸币.
Ben: My fins, I thought they were your fins.
病人:你知道它.那是一个相当猥亵的笑话.
Patient: You know it. Well that's a pretty racy joke.
本:我知道,我哥哥告诉过我.
Ben: I know. My big brother told it to me.
病人:那足够让人道德败坏了.我们还是赌博吧,
Patient: Well that's enough of corrupting the morals of a minor.
你准备好了吗?
Let's get back to gambling. Alright, you ready?
本:好了.
Ben: Ready.
病人:有七点吗?
Patient: Got any sevens?
本:你抓吧.克里斯,吸烟对你有害.
Ben: Go fish. You know Chris, smoking those things is bad for ya.
病人:没事,本.这些雪茄不会伤害我,一点也不.
Patient: Ah, it's alright Bennie. These cigars won't hurt me. Nothing will.
本:你很快要出院了吧?
Ben: So, are you getting out of here real soon.
病人:是的,很快.
Patient: Yeah. Soon.
本:太好了,也许那时候你可以来看我,克里斯?
Ben: Great, cos maybe you can come visit me then. Chris?
病人:该你了,该你了.
Patient: Your turn, your turn.
迈克:嘿,本.你在做什么?
Mike: Hey Ben. What the heck have you been doing?
本:赌博,还有讲一些下流的笑话.
Ben: Gambling and telling dirty jokes.
开萝尔:本,我们一直在找你.
Carol: Ben, we've been looking all over for you.
本:我不知道.
Ben: I didn't know.
迈克:好的,我希望我的傻弟弟没有打扰你.
Mike: Yeah, I hope my stupid brother hasn't been bothering you.
病人:哦,他脖子上倒有点疼痛.
Patient: Oh, he's been a real pain in the neck.
迈克:来吧,本.小宝宝出生了,我们走吧.
Mike: Come on Ben. The new babies here. Let's go.
病人:那就是你的哥哥?他看起来不错,你认为你会得到一个什么呢?小弟弟还是小妹妹?
Patient: That's your big brother? He seems like a neat guy. What do you think you got. A new brother or a new sister?
本:我不介意.
Ben: I don't care.
病人:嘿,我不相信.
Patient: Hey, I don't believe that.
你们去看看吧,快去快去.
Now you go on down and find out what it is. Go go.
本:再见,克里斯.
Ben: Bye Chris.
病人:再见,小老弟.
Patient: So long pal.
麦琪:哦,杰森,她真漂亮.
Maggie: Oh Jason, she's beautiful.
杰森:就像她妈妈.麦琪,你成功了.
Jason: Just like her mother. Oh Maggie, you did it.
麦琪:我们成功了.宝贝,我很抱歉,对你大喊大叫.
Maggie: We did it. And sweetheart, I'm so sorry for all my yelling at you.
杰森:什么喊叫?
Jason: What yelling?
麦琪:我要你知道,我很乐意嫁给你,你可以帮马桶盖竖起来,直到我们老去.
Maggie:  I want you to know that I love being married to you and you can leave the toilet seat up until we are old and grey.
杰森:宝贝,那是你对我说过的最浪漫的话.
Jason: Honey, that's the most romantic thing you have ever said to me.
你们好,对你们的小妹妹问号吧.
Hello, come say hello to your new baby sister.
开萝尔:妹妹.
Carol: Sister.
迈克:是个女孩?你是说我整天期盼,盼来了一个女孩?
Mike: It's a girl? You mean I went through all that for another girl?
开萝尔:嗯,她是一个小天使.
Carol: Oh, she's a little angel.
迈克:你确信它是一个女孩?
Mike: Are you sure it's a girl?
杰森:当然,绝对相信.
Jason: Yeah. Pretty sure.
开萝尔:我可以抱她吗?现在已经打平了.迈克,你想抱她吗?
Carol: Can I hold her? Now it's finally even. Mike, do you want to hold her?
迈克:不,我可能弄疼她.
Mike: No, I might break her or something.
开萝尔:孬种.
Carol: Weenie.
本:大孬种.
Ben: Major weenie.
迈克:好吧,我抱她.喔,她还没有一个保龄球重.我那时候可没这么小.
Mike: Alright I'll hold her. Wow, she weighs less than a bowling ball. I was never this small.
麦琪:你是.
Maggie: Oh you were.
迈克:一个全新的西维尔.我们现在已经有六个人了.我是……
Mike: A whole new Seaver. I guess that makes six of us now. Well I'm...
杰森:成长?
Jason: Growing up?
迈克:好的,我真想不到我会……紧张.
Mike: Yeah. Never thought I'd be this...alergic.
杰森:生活中有些事情是没法计划的,
Jason: Well there are some things in life that no amount of planning can
做不了准备.
ever make you ready for.
麦琪:抱一个小宝宝可能是世界上最重要的事.
Maggie: And holding a new born baby is probably the best one in the whole world.
迈克:嘿,本,你想抱她吗?
Mike: Hey Ben, you want to hold her?
杰森:你现在也是哥哥了.
Jason: You're big brother Ben now.
本:本哥哥.
Ben: Big brother Ben.
杰森:你觉得怎样?
Jason: So what do you think?
本:她很漂亮.
Ben: I think she's cool.
杰森:她很漂亮.
Jason: She's cool.
Maggie: Look Jason, we can't hold off naming her 矢ny longer now.
麦琪:杰森,我们到现在还没给她取名呢?
杰森:是的,我知道,我知道.我们来商量一下,乌玛.
Jason: Yeah, I know I know. Well let's tell the kids the name we agreed
on. Urma
麦琪:我不同意叫乌玛.我同意索非亚.
Maggie: I never agreed to Urma. I agreed to Sophie.
杰森:索非亚.
Jason: Sophie.
迈克:嘿嘿,你们觉得爱泼罗尼亚怎么样?
Mike: Hey, hey, how do you feel about Appleonia?
本:克莉丝,最好叫克莉丝.
Ben: Chris. It's go to be Chris.
麦琪:克莉丝,我喜欢这个名字.
Maggie: Chris. I like that name.
杰森:好的,我也喜欢.你怎么想出来的,本?
Jason: Yeah, I like that name too. Where did you come up with that Ben?
本:那是我认识的一个人的名字,一个朋友.
Ben: It's the name of a guy I know. A friend.
开萝尔:克莉丝 西维尔.
Carol: Chris Seaver.
杰森:克莉丝 西维尔.
Jason: Chris Seaver.
麦琪:克莉丝 西维尔.
Maggie: Christine Seaver.
迈克:听起来像一个名字.
Mike: Sounds like a name.
本:我将成为克莉丝的好哥哥.你们会看到的,我甚至不介意
Ben: I'm going to be a good big brother Chris. You'll see. I don't even mind sharing my
和你分享我的生日.
birthday with you.
杰森:克莉丝 西维尔,八磅四盎司,出生于12点03分.
Jason: Christine Seaver, eight pounds four ounces. Born twelve o three am.
本:12点03分?你意思是明天?我生日的后一天?
Ben: Twelve o three? You mean its tomorrow? The day after my birthday?
杰森:看起来是这样.
Jason: Well that's one way of looking at it.
本:太好了!
Ben: Alright!
杰森:嘿,我差点忘记了.恭喜西维尔先生,来根雪茄.
本:生日快乐,克莉丝.
Jason: Hey, I almost forgot. Congratulations Mr. Seaver. Have a cigar. Ben: Happy Birthday Chris